ATHENA WILBON



SUMMARY

Experienced and effective customer service ambassador with 3+ years of practical skill applied to the field. Self-motivated and hard working Individual. Versatile within the workplace with the ability to work both independently and on a team. Possesses excellent leadership, organizational, communication and time-management abilities. Passionate and motivated to excel within the brand and the opportunity to expand my career within H&M.



EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Charlotte | Charlotte, NC

Pursuing B.A. in Business Marketing

Minoring in Japanese with a 3.2 Grade Point Average and anticipated graduation date of December 2023



EXPERIENCE

Full-Time Sales Advisor

H&M

- -Influence, Lead, Direct and Assist a team of 3 or more associates on both the salesfloor and in Back of House
- -Operating cash registers, managing financial transactions, and opening and closing cash drawers
- -Opening and closing procedures on both the salesfloor and shipment processing
- -Executing proper and effective customer experience via company standards and values
- -Setting and maintaining visual displays to heighten the customer engagement with merchandise
- -Unpacking, sorting, stocking and placing merchandise per store guidelines
- -Balance both Sales profit and observance of all LP practices while performing as the HOD

Assistant Manager- March 2019 to June 2020

Pacific Sunwear (Pacsun)

- Hiring, leading and training a team of 5 or more employees whilst implementing company standards and procedures
- -Schedule making as well as calculating the allocation of hours for each pay period
- Processing and shipping out online orders; maintaining each daily quota
- Overnight Floor set execution and Back-stock organization per visual guidelines
- Performed all register operations, executed morning / nightly Bank deposits and closing reports

Sales Advisor- December 2016 to November 2018

H&M

- -Operating cash registers, managing financial transactions, and balancing drawers
- -Executing proper and effective customer experience via company standards and values
- -Setting and maintaining visual displays to improve engagement with merchandise
- -Unpacking, sorting, stocking and placing merchandise per store guidelines
- -Maintained Sales whilst observing the salesfloor for shrink and all LP security practices throughout the store

Sales Associate- February 2015 to June 2016

Forever 21

- -Greeting and providing assistance to customers
- -Advertising credit cards and loyalty programs with an above 25% success rate
- -Processed monetary transactions via POS totaling several thousand dollars each day
- Constant visual updates

Sales Associate- April 2014 to December 2014

Underground by Journeys

- -Meet and exceed sales quotas via commission based selling
- -Provided a fun, full-service shopping experience to customers
- -Stayed informed of current fashion trends in order to best determine client need